Guide to the Larry LaRocco Collection 1982-1994
Boise State University Library, Special Collections and Archives
- General files, 1
  - Debt for Nature Swaps, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    World Wildlife Federation; Global Ecology
  - Defense, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    Idaho National Guard; Albertsons; Ballistic Missile Defense Organization; Department of Defense; Military Budgets
  - Defense Appropriations (Box 12, Folder 29)
    Air Force Bombing Range; Owyhee County, Idaho
  - Defense Authorization, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 30)
    Idaho National Guard; Gowen Field; Ballistic Missile Defense Organization; Shoshone-Paiute Indians
  - Defense Authorization, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    Bosnia; Haiti
  - Defense Budget, 1993, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Department of Defense; Nuclear Weapons; Department of Education; Military Bases; Strategic Defense Initiative
    H.R.11
  - Defense Budget, 1993: National Guard, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Department of Defense--Appropriations; Idaho--Military Bases
    Statement on floor "National Guard" 6/4/1992
    H.R.5006
  - Defense Budget, 1993: Post-Cold War Spending, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Department of Defense--Appropriations; National Guard; Nuclear Testing; Department of Defense--Research
    H.R.3636; H.R. 2521
  - Defense Budget, 1995, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Department of Defense; National Environmental Policy Act; Gowen Field; Weapon Systems; Department of Energy
    Statement before House Rules Committee, 8/2/1993
    H.R.2401
  - Defense Conversion Initiatives, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Defense: Guard and Reserves, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Idaho National Guard; Gowen Field
  - Democratic Caucus, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Democratic Party, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Democratic Party, 1993 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Democratic Party: Idaho Issues, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    Campaign, 1994; Idaho--Campaign, 1994
  - Department of Commerce, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    International Trade; Idaho--Trade
    Garten, Jeffrey E.
  - Department of Interior, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    Bureau of Land Management; Saylor Creek Range
  - Derivatives, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    Interest Rates; Derivative Securities; Banks and Banking
  - Derivatives Hearing, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    Derivatives Securities; Banks and Banking
    LaWare, John P.
  - Derivatives Safety and Soundness, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    Interest Rates; Securities; Derivative Securities; Banks and Banking
  - Derivatives Safety and Soundness Act of 1994 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    H.R.4170
  - Desert Protection Act, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    Sierra Club
  - Design Innovation and Technology Act, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    Automotive Service Association
    H.R. 1790
  - Disadvantaged Business Enterprise, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    Davis Bacon Act; Transportation
    H.R.2950
  - Domestic Agenda for America, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    Economic Assistance, Domestic
    Thornton, Ray
  - Drawdown, 1991-1994 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    Cascade Reservoir; Dworshak Lake; Salmon; Drawdowns
  - Dredges, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    Army Corps of Engineers; Dredging
  - Drift Nets, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    Driftnets; Fishing--Pacific Ocean; NAFTA--Environmental Aspects
  - Drinking Water, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    Environmental Protection Agency; Radon; Safe Drinking Water Act
  - Drought, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    Agriculture Conservation Program; Idaho--Drought
    Stallings, Richard
  - Drought, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    Irrigation; Water Resources; Environmental Protection Agency; Idaho--Drougt
    Symms, Steve
  - Drought, 1993-1994 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    Water Resources; Droughts
  - Drug Legalization, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    Marijuana; Drug Use; Hemp Industry
  - Dry Beans, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    International Trade; NAFTA: Idaho Bean Commission
  - Dry Pea and Lentil Issues, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    Dry Peas; Lentils; Agriculture; Pesticides
  - Duck Valley Hospital, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Fort Belknap Reservation; Health and Human Services Department; Shoshone-Paiute Indians; Duck Valley Indian Reservation
  - Dworshak Access Proposal: Aquarius, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Dworshak Dam; Clearwater National Forest; Aquarius Research Natural Area
  - Dworshak Dam and Reservoir, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    Energy and Water Development Appropriations; Corps of Engineers; Dworshak Dam; Water Resources
    H.R.4506
  - Earned Income Credit, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Taxation; Income Taxes
  - Earned Income Tax Credit: Congressional Districts Estimates, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Earned Income Tax Credit: LaRocco Mailings, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Income Tax; Tax Credits
  - Earned Income Tax Credit: Miscellaneous, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Earned Income Tax Credit: Response to Leroy, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Earned Income Tax Credit: Sample Mailings, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Eastern Columbia Plateau Aquifer System, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Columbia Basin; Safe Water Drinking Act; Idaho--Aquifers
  - Economic Development Administration, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Agriculture Department; Public Utilities; Rural Electrification
  - Economic Issues, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Budget; Republican Party; Democratic Party; Economic Policy
  - Ecosystem Management, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    Forest Health; Lake Pend Oreille; Grizzly Bears; Bureau of Land Management
  - Ecosystem Management, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    Forest Health
  - Ecosystem Management, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    Forest Health; Timber Sales; Clearcutting; Forest Management
  - Ecoterrorist Activities, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    H.R.473
  - Education, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    Next Century Schools; America 2000; New American Schools Development Corporation; Education
  - Education 2000, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    Idaho--Public Education; Education 2000; Education
    Riley, Richard W.; Evans, Jerry L.
    H.R.1804
  - Education in Idaho, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    Idaho--Education
  - Education Issues: Background, 1993-1994 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    National and Community Service Trust Act; Volunteers; Elementary and Secondary Education Act
    Limbaugh, Rush
    P.L.103-82
  - Education Reform, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    Idaho--Education; Poor--Education; School-to-Work Opportunities Act; Public School Boards; Education
    H.R.4606
  - Education Voting Record, 1991-1994 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Education: Appropriations, 1991,1994 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    Library; Idaho--Libraries
  - Education: Congressional Activities, 1992-1994 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    H.R.3658; H.R.4251; H.R.4316; H.R.6; H.R.3722; H.R.3498
  - Education: Constituent Communication, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    Head Start; Woman, Infants and Children Program (WIC); Fair Labor Standards Act; Volunteers; Developmental Disabilities Act; Education
    H.R.3949
  - Education: News Clippings, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    Campaign, 1994
  - El Salvador, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - El Salvador, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - El Salvador, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    El Salvador; Economic Assistance; Central America
  - El Salvador, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    Economic Assistance; Amnesty International; Central America
    Statement on floor, "Breakthrough for Peace in El Salvador", 10/17/1991
  - El Salvador, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - El Salvador, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Human Rights
  - El Salvador: Committee in Solidarity With the People of .., 1991 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Elk, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Bovine Tuberculosis; Cattle
    H.R.5775
  - Empowering Women, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Women in the Work Force
    Speech "Empowering Women: The Right to Economic Security"
  - Endangered Species Act, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Fish and Wildlife Service; Bull Trout; Spotted Owl
  - Endangered Species Act: Amendment Comparisons, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    H.R.1490; H.R.4045; H.R.2043; S.921
  - Endangered Species Act: Baucus vs. Studds, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Baucus, Max
    S.291
  - Endangered Species Act: Bull Trout, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Endangered Species Act: Foley, Tom, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Endangered Species Act: LaRocco Position, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Endangered Species Act: Mining, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    Clean Water Act; Mines and Mining
  - Endangered Species Act: Policy, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    Fish and Wildlife Service; California--Fires; Wetlands
    Kempthorne, Dirk; Craig, Larry
    H.R.3997; H.R.3978; H.R.141; H.R.1490; H.R.1992; H.R.2043; S.921
  - Endangered Species Act: Process, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    State Government
  - Endangered Species Act: Sportsman, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    Hunter; Fishers; Trappers
  - Endangered Species Act: Studd-Dingell Bill, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Endangered Species Act: Sturgeon, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Endangered Species Act: Tauzin Proposal, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    Bald Eagles
    Tauzin, Billy
    H.R.1490
  - Endangered Species Act: Wildlife Society, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    Public Lands; Bruneau Hot Springs Snail; Salmon; Spotted Owls; Wilderness Society
  - Energy, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    INEL; Radioactive Waste Policy
  - Energy Bill, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    Nuclear Waste Policy Act; Idaho--Energy
  - Energy Resources, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    Power Resources; Nuclear Energy; Alaska--Petroleum; Arctic National Wildlife Refuge
  - Enterprise for the Americas, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    Enterprise for the Americas Initiative Act; Latin America; Developmental Bank; Banks and Banking
    H.R.964
  - Entitlement, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Environmental and Energy Study Conference, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    Global Ecology; Natural Resources
  - Environmental Defense Institute, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 25)
    INEL
  - Environmental Protection Act, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 26)
    H.R.3425
  - Environmental Protection Agency, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    Safe Drinking Water Act
  - Environmental Protection Agency, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Escheatment, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    Equitable Escheatment Act; Securities
    Richards, Ann W.
    H.R.2443
  - Ethanol-Gasahol Fuels, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    Clean Air Act
  - Ethanol/Oxygenate, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    Renewable Oxygenate; Clearn Air Act
  - Ethics, 1991-1994 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    Congress--Ethics; Democratic Party--Ethics; Ethics Reform Act of 1989
    P.L.101-194
  - Ethiopian Grain (TEFF), 1992 (Box 15, Folder 33)
    International Trade; Anti-Apartheid Act
  - Europe, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    International Relations; Northern Ireland; Yugoslavia; Bosnia; Russia
  - Export Controls, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    International Trade; Nonproliferation Treaty
  - Export-Import Bank, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    Macomber, John D.; Kleczka, Gerald D.; Moody, Jim
    H.R.1635
  - Export-Import Bank, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Export-Import Bank, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    International Trade; Banks and Banking
    Macomber, John D.
  - Export-Import Bank, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Export-Import Bank, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    International Trade; Small Business Administration
  - F-15/F-16 Sales, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Arm Sales; Weapon Systems; Defense Industry
  - Fair Credit Reporting Act, 1992-1994 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    Credit Cards; Credit--Governmental Policy; Banks and Banking
    Kennedy, Joseph P. III
  - Fair Credit Reporting Act, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    Credit--Governmental Policy; Consumer Reporting Reform Act; Banks and Banking
  - Fair Credit Reporting Act, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    Credit--Governmental Policy; FBI National Security Exemption; Consumer Reporting Reform Act; Banks and Banking
  - Fair Credit Reporting Act, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    Consumer Reporting Reform Act; Credit Ratings; Credit--Governmental Policy; Banks and Banking
  - Fair Credit Reporting Act, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Fair Credit Reporting Act, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    Credit--Governmental Policy; Banks and Banking
  - Fair Credit Reporting Act, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    Consumer Reporting Reform Act; Credit--Governmental Policy; Banks and Banking
  - Fair Credit Reporting Act, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Fair Credit Reporting Act, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    Consumer Reporting Reform Act; Credit--Governmental Policy; Marketing; Banks and Banking
  - Fair Credit Reporting Act, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Fair Credit Reporting Act, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    Consumer Reporting Reform Act; Banks and Banking
  - Fair Credit Reporting Act, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Fair Trade in Financial Services, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    Fair Trade in Financial Services Act; Banks and Banking
  - Fairness Doctrine, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    Federal Communication Commission
  - Fairness in Broadcasting, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    Freedom in Speech; Fairness in Broadcasting Act; Communication Act of 1934
    H.R.1985
  - Family and Medical Leave Bill, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    Family and Medical Leave Bill; Medical Care
    H.R.2
  - Farm Bill of 1995, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    Agriculture; Rural Development; Idaho--Agriculture; Wheat; Barley; GATT; International Trade
  - Farm Credit, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    Rural Credit and Development Act; Agriculture; Fair Credit Reporting Act; Banks and Banking
    H.R.4129
  - Farm Policy Forum, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    Agriculture; Farm Bill
    Statement to Farm Policy Forum, Spokane, WA, 9-24-1994
  - Farmers Home Administration, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    Rural Development
  - Farmers Home Administration, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Federal Aviation Administration, 1993-1994 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    Air Pilots--Health; Lewiston, Idaho; Agriculture
  - Federal Communications Commission: PR Docket 92-235, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Federal Credit Union, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    Credit Unions
  - Federal Employees, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    Retirement--Government Employees; Insurance Claims; Workman's Compensation
  - Federal Energy Regulatory Commission Bill, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    Federal Power Act
    H.R.649
  - Federal Energy Regulatory Commission Bill, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    Water Resouces; Hydropower Liscensing; Rock Creek; Federal Energy Regulatory Commission; Federal Power Act
    H.R. 649
  - Federal Forage Formula, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    Public Lands--Fees; Grazing
  - Federal Highway Trust Fund, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    Roads and Bridges in Idaho
  - Federal Reserve, 1990-1994 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    Gonzalez, Henry B.
  - Federal Reserves, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    Prime Interest
  - Federal Trade Commission, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    Securities; International Trade
  - Fee Proposal for State Chartered Banks, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    Banks and Banking; Federal Reserve Board
  - Financial Aid Information, 1989-1990 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    Student Aid; Education Department; College Students
    Gilman, Benjamin
  - Financial Derivatives, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    Securities; Interest Rates; Banks and Banking
  - Financial Derivatives, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    Derivatives Securities; Safety and Soundness; Banks and Banking
    H.R.4503
  - Financial Services, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    Financial Services Competitive Act; Financial Services Industry; Banks and Banking
    H.R.4956
  - Flag Protection Amendment, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    American Legion; Flags--United States
  - Food and Drug Administration, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    Nutrition; Agriculture
  - Food Labeling, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    Food and Drug Administration; Food--Labeling
    H.R.2900
  - Foodservice Technology Corporation, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    Morrison Knudsen
  - Foreign Aid, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    Democratic Party; Foreign Aid Authorization
    H.R.2508
  - Foreign Aid, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    International Development Cooperation Act
  - Foreign Aid, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    Agency for International Development
    Obey, David
    H.R.5368
  - Foreign Aid, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    Agency for International Development; Economic Assistance
  - Foreign Aid, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Foreign Aid, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    Bentsen, Lloyd
  - Foreign Aid, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    Peace Corps; Economic Assistance
  - Foreign Aid: Authorization and Appropriations, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    Mondale, Walter F.
  - Foreign Trade, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    International Trade; Mexico; Soviet Union
  - Forest Fires, 1992-1994 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    Drought; Forest Management; Forest Health
  - Forest Frauds, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    Forest Reserves; Forest Service; Timber Harvesting; Timber Sales
    H.R.3745
  - Forest Health, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Forest Health, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    National Forest Health Act
    H.R.229
  - Forest Health, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    Idaho--Forest Reserves
  - Forest Health, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    Forest Ecosystem
  - Forest Health, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    Wildfires
    Lyons, James R.
    Statement Before Joint Hearing on Wildfires and Forest Health, Oct 4, 1994
  - Forest Health, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Forest Health: Amendment, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    Timber
    Statement before the Subcommittee on Forests, Family Farms, and Energy 8/6/1992
    H.R.4980
  - Forest Health: Blue Mountains, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    Forest Management; East Side Forest Health Assessment; Blue Mountains, Oregon; Forest Reserves--Washington; Forest Reserves--Oregon
  - Forest Health: Boise Symposium, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Forest Health: Co-Sponsors, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Forest Health: Correspondence and Memos, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    Forest Fires; National Forest Health Act; Idaho--Constituent Communications; Forest Health
    Mitchell, Ron; Craig, Larry E.
    H.R.229; H.R.4980
  - Forest Health: Correspondence, Environmental, 1992-1994 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Forest Health: Correspondence, General, 1992-1994 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Nez Perce Indians
  - Forest Health: Correspondence, Industry, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Forest Health: Emergency Salvage Effort, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    Timber Salvage; Environmental Policy Acth
  - Forest Health: "Green Slips", 1992 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    Timber Sales; Fuelwood; Payette National Forest
  - Forest Health: Hearing, August 30, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    Timber Sales; Forest Fires
    Andrus, Cecil B.; Craig, Larry E.
    H.R.4980; H.R.229
  - Forest Health: Hearing, 1992 July 1 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    Idaho--Forest Reserves; Land Use
    Statement before Subcommittee on Forest, Family Farms and Energy, 7/1/1992
  - Forest Health: Hearing, 1992 June 30 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Forest Health: Hearing, 1992 May 23 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Forest Health: Hearing, 1994 October 4 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    Forest Fires; Logging
  - Forest Health: Hearing, 1992 September 23 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    Land Use; Logging
    Statement before Subcommittee on General Oversight and California Desert Lands, 9/23/1992
  - Forest Health: Hearing, 1994 September 29 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    Statement before Subcommittee on Specialty Crops and natural Resources, 9/29/1994
    H.R.5007
  - Forest Health: Idaho, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    Boise National Forest; Idaho--Forest Reserves
    Idaho SJM 104
  - Forest Health: Idaho, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    Forest Fires; Idaho--Forest Reserves
  - Forest Health: Idaho, Lawsuit, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    Sierra Club Legal Defense Fund; Pacific Rivers Council; Wilderness Society; Citizen Suits
  - Forest Health: Legislation, 1992-1993 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    National Forest Health Act; Paper Products
  - Forest Health: Legislation, 1992-1994 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    Rangeland Renewable Resources Planning Act; Timber Sales; Forest Fires
    Packwood, Robert
    S.1156; S.459; H.R.2459; H.R.5503
  - Forest Health: Original Bill, 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    National Forest Health Act; Timber Sales
  - Forest Health: Photographs, undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
    Oregon--Forest Reserves; Idaho--Forest Reserves
  - Forest Health: Press, 1992-1994 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    Timber Salvage; National Forest Health Act; Timber Sales
  - Forest Health: Press, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    Forest Fires; Timber Sales
  - Forest Health: Priest Lake Workshop, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    Salvage
  - Forest Health: Productivity, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    Idaho--Forest Reserves; Forest Fires
    Statement before Subcommittee on Agricultural Research, Conservation and General Legislation Boise, Idaho 8/29/1994
  - Forest Health: Related Laws, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    Idaho--Forest Practices Act; Renewable Resources; Public Lands; Forest Reserves; Forest Management
  - Forest Health: Reports, 1991-1994 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Forest Health: Spokane Conference, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    National Forest Health Act; Timber Salvage
    Speech to Conference on Forest Health and Fire Danger in Inland Western Forests 9/9/1994
  - Forest Health: Statements and Speeches, 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    Forest Health Act; Timber Salvage
    Amdrus, Cecil B.
    Statement on Floor on the National Forest Health Act 4/28/1992, 6/9/1993, 6/1/1993, 4/29/1993; Statement on Floor Concerning Timber Salvage; Speech to Logging
  - Forest Health: Survey, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    Timber Salvage
  - Forest Health: Tour, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    Clean Water Act; Montana--Forest Reserves--Tours; Idaho--Forest Reserves--Tours
  - Forest Plans, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    Forest Service
  - Forest Service, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Idaho State Industrial Commission; Federal Land Policy and Management Act; Grazing; Public Lands
    Logan, Lanham
    H.R.4065; H.R.473
  - Forest Service Chief, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    Thomas, Jack Ward; Lyons, James R.
    Speech "Repositioning the Forest Service Benefits and Risks" 12/14/1993
  - Forest Service Reform, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Forest Service Reform, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    Forest Health; Natural Resources
    Lyons, Jim
  - Forest Service Reform, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    Ecosystems; Forest Reserves; Paper Products
  - Forest Summit, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    Forest Health; Forest Reserves
  - Former USSR, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    International Monetary Fund; World Bank; Russia
    Mulford, David; Oakar, Mary Rose
  - Frank Church-River of No Return Wilderness Bills, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    National Wildlife Refuge Wilderness Management Act; Wilderness Areas
    H.R.4327
  - Frank Church-River of No Return Wilderness Correspondence, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    Wilderness Areas; Forest Service; Idaho Conservation League
    Burns, John E.
  - Frank Church-River of No Return Wilderness Hearing, 1992 June 23 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    River Guides; National Forest Wilderness Management Act; Idaho Conservation League; Hunting Guides
    H.R.4325
  - Frank Church-River of No Return Wilderness Press, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    Wilderness Areas; Forest Service
  - Frank Church-River of No Return Wilderness Reports, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    Frank Church River of No Return Wilderness Area
  - Frank Church-River of No Return Wilderness Reports, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Frank Church-River of No Return Wilderness Statements, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    Vento, Bruce F.; Church, Frank
    Speech to Subcommittee on National Parks and Public Lands June 23, 1992
  - Frank Church-River of No Return Wilderness Symposium, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    Frank Church River of No Return Wilderness Area; National Forest Wilderness Management Act
    Speech to Symposium February 28, 1992